Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Hope Mission (Yale)
    - History, 1955-1971 (Box 109, Folder 3268)
    - Minutes
      - 1923-1936 (Box 109, Folder 3269)
      - 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 3270)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 109, Folder 3271)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 109, Folder 3272)
      - 1940-1944 (Box 109, Folder 3273)
      - 1951-1959 (Box 110, Folder 3274)
      - 1960-1964 (Box 110, Folder 3275)
    - Minutes, Financial Statements, etc, 1974-1978 (Box 110, Folder 3276 - 3277)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 110, Folder 3278)
    - Notes, circa 1970's (Box 110, Folder 3279)
    - Pamphlet, undated (Box 110, Folder 3280)
    - Reports, 1929 (Box 110, Folder 3281)
    - Resolutions, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 3282)
    - A Sketch of the Life and Character of William W. Borden, undated (Box 110, Folder 3283)
    - Superintendent's Reports
      - 1923-1926 (Box 110, Folder 3284)
      - 1927-1929 (Box 110, Folder 3285)
      - 1929-1931 (Box 110, Folder 3286)
      - 1932-1935 (Box 110, Folder 3287)
      - 1936-1938 (Box 110, Folder 3288)
    - Treasurer's Reports, Financial Information and Records, 1924-1929 (Box 110, Folder 3289)
    - Treasurer's Reports, Financial Information and Records, 1930-1933 (Box 110, Folder 3290)
    - Treasurer's Reports, Financial Information and Records, 1934-1938 (Box 110, Folder 3291)
    - Union Trust Portfolio Report, 1976-1977 (Box 110, Folder 3292)
  - Houseware Purchases, 1956 (Box 110A, Folder 3293)
  - Howard University, Visit to, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 3294)
  - Howard University Weekend, 1948 (Box 110, Folder 3295)
  - Hsiangya Medical College Report, 1939 (Box 110, Folder 3296)
  - Inclusive Student Movement, undated (Box 110, Folder 3297)
  - Indianapolis Convention, 1935-1936 (Box 110, Folder 3298)
  - Industrial Movement, undated (Box 110, Folder 3299)
  - Industrial Relations Club, 1936 (Box 110, Folder 3300)
  - Industrial Service Movement, 1919-1921 (Box 110, Folder 3301 - 3302)
  - Industrial Work, 1914-1915 (Box 110, Folder 3303)
  - Information (Dwight Hall), 1962-1964 (Box 110, Folder 3304)
  - Information about Students Entering Yale, 1917-1918 (Box 110, Folder 3305)
  - Institute for American Democracy, 1945-1946 (Box 110, Folder 3306)
  - Institute for Independent Schools, 1956-1957 (Box 110, Folder 3307)
  - Institute for Independent Schools, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 3308)
  - Institute of International Education, 1943 (Box 110, Folder 3309)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1942 (Box 111, Folder 3310)
  - Institute of Social Science, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 3311)
  - Institute of Social Science, the Consultative Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 111, Folder 3312)
  - Interchurch World Movement, 1920 (Box 111, Folder 3313)
  - Intercollegian
    - no date (Box 111, Folder 3314)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 111, Folder 3315)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 111, Folder 3316)
    - 1943 (Box 111, Folder 3317)
    - 1944 (Box 111, Folder 3318)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 111, Folder 3319)
    - 1945 (Box 111, Folder 3320)
    - 1960 (Box 111, Folder 3321)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 111, Folder 3322)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 111, Folder 3323)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 111, Folder 3324)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 111, Folder 3325)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 111, Folder 3326)
    - 1966 (Box 111, Folder 3327)
    - Intercollegian and Far Horizons, 1939-1940 (Box 111, Folder 3328)
    - Intercollegian Committee, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 3329)
    - Intercollegian Committee, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 3330)
  - Intercollegiate Disarmament Council, 1933 (Box 111, Folder 3331)
  - Intercollegiate YMCA of New York, 1916 (Box 111, Folder 3332)
  - Interfaith Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 111, Folder 3333)
  - Intern Evaluation, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 3334)
  - International Christian Press and Information Service, 1944 (Box 111, Folder 3335)
  - International Committee of YMCA
    - 1914-1915 (Box 111, Folder 3336)
    - 1915 (Box 111, Folder 3337)
    - 1916 (Box 111, Folder 3338)
    - 1918 (Box 112, Folder 3339)
    - 1918 (Box 112, Folder 3340)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 112, Folder 3341 - 3342)
  - Conferences, 1915 (Box 112, Folder 3343)
  - International Consultation Group for Peace and Disarmament, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 3344)
  - International Club, 1941-1948 (Box 112, Folder 3345 - 3348)
  - International Club: Lists of Foreign Students, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 3349)
  - International Missionary Council, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 3350)
  - International Missionary Council, Jerusalem Meeting, 1928 (Box 112, Folder 3351)
  - International Student Center
    - 1950 (Box 112, Folder 3352)
    - 1951 (Box 112, Folder 3353)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 112, Folder 3354)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 3355)
    - 1954 (Box 113, Folder 3356)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 113, Folder 3357)
    - 1960 (Box 113, Folder 3358)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 113, Folder 3359)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 3360)
  - International Student Committee, 1938 (Box 113, Folder 3361)
  - International Student Lists, 1943-1945 (Box 113, Folder 3362 - 3363)
  - International Student Service, undated (Box 113, Folder 3364)
  - International Student Service: Chinese University Relief, 1937-1938 (Box 113, Folder 3365)
  - International Students, 1942 (Box 113, Folder 3366)
  - International Students at Yale, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 3367)
  - International Students' Sprint Promenade, 1937 (Box 113, Folder 3368)
  - International YMCA Convention at Cleveland, Ohio, 1916 (Box 113, Folder 3369)
  - Internship Project, circa 1970's (Box 113, Folder 3370)
  - Inter-racial Commission, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 3371)
  - Inter-religious Council, undated (Box 113, Folder 3372)
  - Inter-religious Council, 1944-1945 (Box 113, Folder 3373)
  - Interseminary Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 3374)
  - Interseminary Movement, 1945-1946 (Box 113, Folder 3375)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 3376)
  - Interview/Background Material, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 3377)
  - Investments
    - 1942 (Box 113, Folder 3378)
    - 1977 (Box 113, Folder 3379)
    - 1978 (Box 113, Folder 3380)
    - 1979 (Box 113, Folder 3381)
  - Investments (South Africa)
    - 1977 (Box 114, Folder 3382)
    - 1978 (Box 114, Folder 3383 - 3385)
    - 1979 (Box 114, Folder 3386)
  - Jaffrey Conference, undated (Box 114, Folder 3387)
  - Japanese Americans
    - 1943-1944 (Box 114, Folder 3388)
    - 1944 (Box 114, Folder 3389 - 3390)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 114, Folder 3391)
  - Japanese Relocation, 1944-1945 (Box 114, Folder 3392 - 3393)
  - Japanese Students' Christian Association, 1941 (Box 114, Folder 3394)
  - Jerusalem, 1928 (Box 114, Folder 3395)
  - Jewish-Christian Dialogue, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 3396)
  - Job Description Executive Director Christian Community Action, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3397)
  - Joint Policy Council, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 3398)
  - Jonathan Edwards College Invitation, circa 1942 (Box 114, Folder 3399)
  - Junior Cabinet, 1961-1962 (Box 114, Folder 3400)
  - Junior Graduate YMCA, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 3401)
  - Junior Work Camps, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 3402)
  - Kansas City: Student Volunteer Conference, 1913-1914 (Box 114, Folder 3403)
  - Kennedy School of Missions, circa 1915 (Box 114, Folder 3404)
  - King, Martin Luther, Dr. Memorial, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 3405)
  - Koo, T. Z. Visit: World Tour Preparations, 1945 (Box 115, Folder 3406 - 3407)
  - Labor Legislation, 1933-1934 (Box 115, Folder 3408)
  - Labor Legislation: Elmore Jackson, 1933 (Box 115, Folder 3409)
  - Law School of Religion, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 3410)
  - Laymen's Missionary Movement
    - no date (Box 115, Folder 3411)
    - 1931 (Box 115, Folder 3412)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 115, Folder 3413)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 115, Folder 3414)
    - 1941 (Box 115, Folder 3415)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 115, Folder 3416)
    - 1946 (Box 115, Folder 3417)
  - Lead Paint Ordinance, 1973-1974 (Box 115, Folder 3418)
  - League of Nations Campaign in New Haven, 1934 (Box 115, Folder 3419)
  - Lecture Series, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 3420)
  - Lecture Series: "Religious Pluralism in a Democratic America", circa 1960 (Box 115, Folder 3421)
  - Lecture Series (Murray Stein), 1965 (Box 115, Folder 3422)
  - Lecture: "Tongues", 1963 (Box 115, Folder 3423)
  - Legislative Internship Program, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 3424)
  - Letter to Parents, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 3425)
  - Liberia Work Camp, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 3426)
  - Library, circa 1950's (Box 115, Folder 3427)
  - Link Leaders, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 3428)
  - Liquor Problem, 1933 (Box 115, Folder 3429)
  - Lisle Fellowships, 1941 (Box 115, Folder 3430)
  - List of Members, 1952 (Box 115, Folder 3431)
  - List of Preparatory Schools with Masters, undated (Box 115, Folder 3432)
  - Lists
    - no date (Box 115, Folder 3433)
    - 1901-1912 (Box 115, Folder 3434)
    - circa 1914 (Box 115, Folder 3435)
    - circa 1915 (Box 115, Folder 3436)
    - 1915-1921 (Box 115, Folder 3437)
    - 1916-1923 (Box 115, Folder 3438)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 116, Folder 3439)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 116, Folder 3440)
    - circa 1925-1926 (Box 116, Folder 3441)
    - 1930's (Box 116, Folder 3442)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 116, Folder 3443)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 116, Folder 3444)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 116, Folder 3445)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 116, Folder 3446)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 116, Folder 3447)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 116, Folder 3448)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 116, Folder 3449)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 3450)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 116, Folder 3451)
    - 1940's (Box 116, Folder 3452 - 3453)
    - 1940 (Box 116, Folder 3454)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 3455)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 116, Folder 3456)
    - 1942 (Box 116, Folder 3457)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 116, Folder 3458)
    - 1943 (Box 116, Folder 3459)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 116, Folder 3460)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 117, Folder 3461)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 117, Folder 3462)
    - Circa 1980 (Box 117, Folder 3463)
  - Lists of Students in Dwight Hall Organizations, undated (Box 117, Folder 3464)
  - Literature and Songs about Christian Faith, 1936-1938 (Box 117, Folder 3465)
  - Louis' Lunch, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 3466)
  - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3467)
  - Lutheran Student Association, 1955-1956 (Box 117, Folder 3468)
  - Magee, John House, undated (Box 117, Folder 3469)
  - Mail from Servicemen, 1944-1945 (Box 117, Folder 3470)
  - Maintenance, 1955-1956 (Box 117, Folder 3471)
  - Manuscript of a Book Chapter: "Assumptions and the Creative Process", undated (Box 117, Folder 3472)
  - March Fourteenth Group, 1932 (Box 117, Folder 3473)
  - Mayoral Race: Al Webber, 1971-1973 (Box 117, Folder 3474)
  - "Meals on Wheels", undated (Box 117, Folder 3475)
  - Medical Center, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 3476)
  - Medical Conference, 1935-1936 (Box 117, Folder 3477)
  - Meetings
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane, 1919-1920 (Box 117, Folder 3478)
    - Drum, Charles R., circa 1917 (Box 117, Folder 3479)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 3480 - 3482)
    - Goldenberg, Ira, 1969 (Box 117, Folder 3483)
    - McKee, 1930 (Box 117, Folder 3484)
    - 1934 (Box 117, Folder 3485)
  - Meetings Before College Opened, 1914-1918 (Box 117, Folder 3486)
  - Mellon: Old Dominion Foundation, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 3487)
  - Members of the Governing Board, 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 3488)
  - Membership Listing, undated (Box 118, Folder 3489)
  - Memorabilia, 1933 (Box 118, Folder 3490)
  - Memos: New Haven, 1970's (Box 118, Folder 3491)
  - Men Abroad, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 3492)
  - Men of Science: Prisoners of War, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 3493)
  - Mental Health in New Haven Area, 1961-1962 (Box 118, Folder 3494)
  - Mentally Retarded Children, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 3495)
  - Methodist: The Wesley Foundation at Yale, undated (Box 118, Folder 3496)
  - Michigan Campaign, 1914-1915 (Box 118, Folder 3497)
  - Middle Atlantic Field Council, 1931 (Box 118, Folder 3498)
  - Migratory Labor: Eric H. Thomson, 1936-1937 (Box 118, Folder 3499)
  - Milk Bar
    - 1932 (Box 118, Folder 3500)
    - 1937 (Box 118, Folder 3501)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 118, Folder 3502)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 118, Folder 3503)
    - 1939-1941 (Box 118, Folder 3504)
    - 1942 (Box 118, Folder 3505)
  - The Mill, 1926 (Box 118, Folder 3506)
  - Mill Fund, 1927-1928 (Box 118, Folder 3507)
  - Mimeographs
    - 1960 (Box 118, Folder 3508)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 118, Folder 3509 - 3510)
    - 1962 (Box 118, Folder 3511)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 118, Folder 3512)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 119, Folder 3513)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 119, Folder 3514 - 3515)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 119, Folder 3516)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 119, Folder 3517)
    - 1969 (Box 119, Folder 3518)
  - Ministers' Group, 1943 (Box 120, Folder 3519)
  - Ministers' Group, 1943-1944 (Box 120, Folder 3520)
  - Ministers' Group, 1944 (Box 120, Folder 3521)
  - Ministers' Meeting, 1940's (Box 120, Folder 3522)
  - Ministers' No War Committee, 1941 (Box 120, Folder 3523)
  - Ministers, Yale in Connecticut, undated (Box 120, Folder 3524)
  - Ministry of the Laity Wider City Parish, 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 3525)
  - Minutes (various), 1949 (Box 120, Folder 3526)
  - Minutes, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 3527)
  - Miscellaneous
    - no date (Box 120, Folder 3528)
    - 1910-1916 (Box 120, Folder 3529)
    - 1917 (Box 120, Folder 3530)
    - 1918 (Box 120, Folder 3531)
    - 1919 (Box 120, Folder 3532)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 120, Folder 3533)
    - circa 1926 (Box 120, Folder 3534)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 120, Folder 3535)
    - 1930's (Box 120, Folder 3536)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 120, Folder 3537)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 120, Folder 3538)
    - 1935 (Box 120, Folder 3539)
    - circa 1935-1938 (Box 120, Folder 3540)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 120, Folder 3541)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 120, Folder 3542)
    - 1939 (Box 120, Folder 3543)
    - 1940 (Box 120, Folder 3544)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 120, Folder 3545)
    - 1944 (Box 120, Folder 3546)
    - 1945 (Box 120, Folder 3547)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 120, Folder 3548)
    - 1950's (Box 120, Folder 3549)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 120, Folder 3550)
    - 1959 (Box 120, Folder 3551)
    - circa 1960's (Box 120, Folder 3552)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 121, Folder 3553)
    - 1969 (Box 121, Folder 3554)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 121, Folder 3555)
    - 1970 (Box 121, Folder 3556)
    - circa 1970's (Box 121, Folder 3557)
    - 1970's (Box 121, Folder 3558)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 121, Folder 3559)
    - Writings: Authors Unknown, 1925-1926 (Box 121, Folder 3560)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Lists
    - no date (Box 121, Folder 3561)
    - 1920's (Box 121, Folder 3562)
    - 1926 (Box 121, Folder 3563)
    - 1933 (Box 121, Folder 3564)
  - Missionary Education Movement, 1928 (Box 121, Folder 3565)
  - Missionary List, 1926 (Box 121, Folder 3566)
  - Missions
    - no date (Box 121, Folder 3567)
    - 1915 (Box 121, Folder 3568)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 121, Folder 3569)
    - Illinois Study, 1914-1915 (Box 121, Folder 3570)
    - Meetings for Interest in Missions, 1915 (Box 121, Folder 3571)
    - Positions Open, Men Wanted, 1915 (Box 121, Folder 3572)
  - Mory's, circa 1970's (Box 121, Folder 3573)
  - Move to Old Library, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 3574)
  - Movement for Dry Class Reunions, 1917 (Box 121, Folder 3575)
  - Movement for World Christianity, 1937 (Box 121, Folder 3576)
  - Movies, 1944 (Box 121, Folder 3577)
  - Movies, 1945 (Box 121, Folder 3578)
  - Multiplex Fixture Display Company, 1919 (Box 121, Folder 3579)
  - Municipal Services, 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 3580)
  - Music Room, 1939-1940 (Box 122, Folder 3581)
  - Nanking Theological, 1931-1932 (Box 122, Folder 3582)
  - National Assembly of Student Christian Associations, 1937 (Box 122, Folder 3583)
  - National Assembly of Student Christian Associations: Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1937-1938 (Box 122, Folder 3584)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 3585)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 3586)
  - National Association of College and University Chaplains
    - 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 3587)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 122, Folder 3588)
    - 1959 (Box 122, Folder 3589)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 122, Folder 3590)
  - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials, 1949 (Box 122, Folder 3591)
  - National Bible Institute, 1916 (Box 122, Folder 3592)
  - National Bible Institute, 1928 (Box 122, Folder 3593)
  - National Commission on Consultations about Student Christian Work, 1934 (Box 122, Folder 3594)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 3595)
  - National Conference of Jews and Christians, 1937 (Box 122, Folder 3596)
  - National Consumers League, 1932-1933 (Box 122, Folder 3597)
  - National Council for Conscientious Objectors, 1942 (Box 122, Folder 3598)
  - National Council of Student Associations, 1929-1930 (Box 122, Folder 3599)
  - National Council of Student Christian Associations
    - 1932-1939 (Box 122, Folder 3600)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 122, Folder 3601)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 122, Folder 3602)
    - 1944 (Box 122, Folder 3603)
    - 1945 (Box 122, Folder 3604)
    - 1945 (Box 122, Folder 3605)
    - 1945 (Box 122, Folder 3606)
    - Committee on Constitutional Revision, 1940 (Box 122, Folder 3607)
    - Finances, 1943-1945 (Box 122, Folder 3608)
    - Personal, 1943 (Box 123, Folder 3609)
  - National Council of YMCA
    - 1927 (Box 123, Folder 3610)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 123, Folder 3611)
    - 1933 (Box 123, Folder 3612)
    - 1944 (Box 123, Folder 3613)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 123, Folder 3614)
    - 1951 (Box 123, Folder 3615)
    - 1962 (Box 123, Folder 3616)
    - Committee on Financial Support, 1943-1944 (Box 123, Folder 3617)
  - National Council on Religion, 1943-1945 (Box 123, Folder 3618)
  - National Council on Religion in Higher Education
    - 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 3619)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 123, Folder 3620)
    - 1945 (Box 123, Folder 3621)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council
    - 1936-1937 (Box 123, Folder 3622)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 123, Folder 3623)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 123, Folder 3624)
    - 1940 (Box 123, Folder 3625 - 3627)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 123, Folder 3628)
    - 1944 (Box 123, Folder 3629)
    - 1945 (Box 124, Folder 3630)
    - 1950 (Box 124, Folder 3631)
    - Administrative Committee: Minutes, 1938 (Box 124, Folder 3632)
  - National Student Association
    - 1950 (Box 124, Folder 3633)
    - Circa 1949 (Box 124, Folder 3634)
    - D.P. Students (Displaced Person), 1948 (Box 124, Folder 3635)
    - Finance, 1948-1949 (Box 124, Folder 3636)
    - Mailing Lists for Information Bureau, Region, etcirca, 1947-1949 (Box 124, Folder 3637)
    - Miscellany, 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 3638)
    - N.E.circa Minutes, 1949 (Box 124, Folder 3639)
    - Policy: National, 1949-1950 (Box 124, Folder 3640)
    - Report and Minutes to the Third National Student Congress, 1950 (Box 124, Folder 3641)
    - Vocational Guidance, 1949-1950 (Box 124, Folder 3642)
    - Work Study Travel, Travel (General), Summer Abroad, 1950 (Box 124, Folder 3643)
    - Working Papers, 1950 (Box 124, Folder 3644)
  - National Student Christian Federation, 1965 (Box 124, Folder 3645)
  - National Student Council, undated (Box 124, Folder 3646)
  - National Student Council of YMCA
    - 1928 (Box 124, Folder 3647)
    - 1938 (Box 124, Folder 3648)
    - 1944 (Box 124, Folder 3649)
    - 1945 (Box 124, Folder 3650)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 124, Folder 3651)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 3652)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 124, Folder 3653)
    - 1953 (Box 124, Folder 3654)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 124, Folder 3655)
    - 1959 (Box 124, Folder 3656)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 125, Folder 3657)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 125, Folder 3658)
    - Administrative Committee, 1943 (Box 125, Folder 3659)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 125, Folder 3660)
    - Financial, 1945-1946 (Box 125, Folder 3661 - 3662)
    - Restoration Fund, 1945-1946 (Box 125, Folder 3663)
    - Statements, 1945-1946 (Box 125, Folder 3664)
  - National Student Division Committee, 1939 (Box 125, Folder 3665)
  - National Thrift Week Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 125, Folder 3666)
  - National Volunteer Service, 1940 (Box 125, Folder 3667)
  - National War Work Council, 1918 (Box 125, Folder 3668)
  - National War Work Council: Shedd, Clarence P., 1919 (Box 125, Folder 3669)
  - National Women's Trade Union, 1937 (Box 125, Folder 3670)
  - Nationalist Press Association, 1939 (Box 125, Folder 3671)
  - New Departure Fish and Game Club, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 3672)
  - New Departure Fish and Game Club, 1939-1940 (Box 125, Folder 3673)
  - New England Christian Association, 1931-1932 (Box 125, Folder 3674)
  - New England Commission on College Work, 1944 (Box 125, Folder 3675)
  - New England Council, undated (Box 125, Folder 3676)
  - New England Field Council
    - 1926 (Box 125, Folder 3677)
    - 1927 (Box 125, Folder 3678)
    - 1929 (Box 126, Folder 3679)
    - 1931 (Box 126, Folder 3680)
    - 1934 (Box 126, Folder 3681)
  - New England Institute of International Relations, 1932 (Box 126, Folder 3682)
  - New England Preparatory Schools: Mid-Winter Conference (Seventh), 1931-1932 (Box 126, Folder 3683)
  - New England Student Christian Movement, 1933-1935 (Box 126, Folder 3684)
  - New England Student Christian Movement, 1936-1937 (Box 126, Folder 3685)
  - New England Student Christian Movement, 1960-1962 (Box 126, Folder 3686)
  - New England Student Christian Movement, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 3687)
  - New England Student Committee, 1929 (Box 126, Folder 3688)
  - New England Student Office, undated (Box 126, Folder 3689)
  - New England Student YMCA Income, 1945 (Box 126, Folder 3690)
  - Newhallville Project, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 3691)
  - New Haven Charter Revision, 1971-1974 (Box 126, Folder 3692)
  - New Haven Churches, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 3693)
  - New Haven Churches, 1937 (Box 126, Folder 3694)
  - New Haven City Politics, undated (Box 126, Folder 3695)
  - New Haven, Correspondence Concerning Work in, 1916 (Box 126, Folder 3696)
  - New Haven Council of Churches
    - 1936-1937 (Box 126, Folder 3697)
    - 1937 (Box 126, Folder 3698)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 126, Folder 3699)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 126, Folder 3700)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 126, Folder 3701)
    - 1941 (Box 126, Folder 3702)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 126, Folder 3703)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 126, Folder 3704)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 126, Folder 3705)
    - 1945 (Box 126, Folder 3706)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 126, Folder 3707)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 126, Folder 3708)
  - News Letters, 1937-1938 (Box 126, Folder 3709)
  - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1933 (Box 126, Folder 3710)
  - New Haven Democratic Primary, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 3711)
  - New Haven Food Co-op, circa 1970's (Box 126, Folder 3712)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 126, Folder 3713)
  - New Haven Freedom Center, 1963-1964 (Box 126, Folder 3714)
  - New Haven Halfway House, 1975-1976 (Box 126, Folder 3715)
  - New Haven Halfway Houses, 1977-1978 (Box 126A, Folder 3716 - 3717)
  - New Haven Halfway Houses, 1979-1980 (Box 126, Folder 3718)
  - New Haven Peace Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 127, Folder 3719)
  - New Haven People's Center, circa 1970's (Box 127, Folder 3720)
  - New Haven Printing Company, 1920-1921 (Box 127, Folder 3721)
  - New Haven Public Library, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 3722)
  - New Haven Scholarship Fund, 1977 (Box 127, Folder 3723)
  - New Haven: Summary of the Important Provisions of the Charter of the City of New Haven and Amendments, 1784-1948 (Box 127, Folder 3724)
  - New Haven YMCA, 1938 (Box 127, Folder 3725)
  - New Orthodoxy, 1933 (Box 127, Folder 3726)
  - New Students, 1917-1918 (Box 127, Folder 3727)
  - New York Trust Company, 1941 (Box 127, Folder 3728)
  - New York University Christian Association, 1942 (Box 127, Folder 3729)
  - Newsletter
    - 1935 (Box 127, Folder 3730)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 127, Folder 3731)
    - 1949 (Box 127, Folder 3732)